{
    "id": "0e813f977df54a9dbe040de8fe9194f9",
    "title": "Identify the verb and the tense",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "98a61c7b1cf441a984c089089956a862",
            "title": "Identify The Tense",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The river flows under the bridge.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple present",
                        "Simple past",
                        "Present perfect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will answer his letter tonight.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple present",
                        "Simple future",
                        "Future perfect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It has been raining all night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Present perfect",
                        "Present perfect continuous",
                        "Past perfect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had finished before he came.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple past",
                        "Present perfect",
                        "Past perfect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He takes little pride in his work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple present",
                        "Present perfect",
                        "Simple past"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "By this time tomorrow, I will have reached my home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple future",
                        "Future perfect",
                        "Future perfect continuous"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mike is waiting for us.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple present",
                        "Present continuous",
                        "Simple past"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am hoping to get a raise.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple present",
                        "Present continuous",
                        "Simple past"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will have plenty of time tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple future",
                        "Future perfect",
                        "Future continuous"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have heard a strange story.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Simple present",
                        "Present perfect",
                        "Present continuous"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}